星球大战
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     哈里星球      Riverside152      星星与野狗
校对     星星与野狗
时间轴     caroline
后期     CK
总监     星星与野狗
曼达人  我收到你的讯息了  好消息啊
Mando. I've received your transmission. Wonderful news.
你返程时  直接把猎物送交给客人吧
Upon your return, deliver the quarry directly to the client.
我不知道他是想要吃了它还是把它挂墙上
I have no idea if he wants to eat it or hang it on his wall,
反正他抓耳挠腮地等呢
but he's very antsy.
一路平安  你知道去哪找我
Safe passage! You know where to find me.
这不是玩具
It's not a toy.
你当心点
Easy with that.
你才当心点
You take it easy.
对
Yes!
对  对  对
Yes, yes, yes!
对
Yes.
非常健康  对
Very healthy. Yes.
你果然名不虚传
Your reputation was not unwarranted.
你给出去多少个追踪器
How many fobs did you give out?
它对我至关重要
This asset was of extreme importance to me.
我得要保证我能拿到它
I had to ensure its delivery.
但谁是胜利者...
But to the winner...
奖励就归谁
Go the spoils.
小小的猎物  如此巨额的赏金
Such a large bounty for such a small package.
你准备拿它做什么
What are your plans for it?
你这样成名的人问这个不太符合身份啊
How uncharacteristic of one of your reputation.
你已经拿了佣金和赏金
You have taken both commission and payment.
《公会章程》不是规定
Is it not the Code of the Guild
这些事就已经当不存在了吗
that these events are now forgotten?
那曼达洛铁足够
That Beskar is enough to make
给你换副不错的铠甲了
a handsome replacement for your armor.
不幸的是  在当前的艰难岁月找到个曼达洛人
Unfortunately, finding a Mandalorian in these trying times
要比找到曼达洛铁难得多
is more difficult than finding the steel.
曼达洛人
第一季  第三集
第三章
罪恶
这个数量可以锻造成很多形状
This amount can be shaped many ways.
我的铠甲不太结实了
My armor has lost its integrity.
我可能又要重新做了
I may need to begin again.
确实  我可以锻造出完整的胸甲
Indeed. I can form a full cuirass.
这会与你的身份相符
This would be in order for your station.
我荣幸之至
That would be a great honor.
我必须警告你  它会非常惹眼的
I must warn you. It will draw many eyes.
这些是在帝国的熔炉里炼出来的
These were cast in an Imperial smelter.
是绝地大屠杀中掠夺来的
These are the spoils of the Great Purge.
而大屠杀正是我们像沙鼠一样隐居的根源
The reason that we live hidden like sand rats.
我们的隐秘让我们得以生存
Our secrecy is our survival.
我们的生存让我们拥有力量
Our survival is our strength.
从前我们的力量来自于我们的数量
Our strength was once in our numbers.
现在我们不见天日地苟且
Now we live in the shadows
只能一个一个地单独到地面上去
and only come above ground one at a time.
我们的世界被帝国给粉碎了
Our world was shattered by the Empire,
而这个懦夫还与之同流合污
with whom this coward shares tables.
帝国已经不存在了
The Empire is no longer.
而曼达洛铁又回来了
And the Beskar has returned.
当你选择了以曼达洛之道行事
When one chooses to walk the Way of the Mandalore,
你既是猎人也是猎物
you are both hunter and prey.
选择这样的生存之道的人怎么可能是懦夫呢
How can one be a coward if one chooses this way of life?
你取下过头盔吗
Have you ever removed your helmet?
没有
No.
被别人取下来过吗
Has it ever been removed by others?
从来没有
Never.
此乃正道
This is the Way.
怎么受的伤
What caused this damage?
泥角兽
A mudhorn.
泥角兽已经成为了你的印记
Then you have earned the Mudhorn as your signet.
我会制作完成
I shall craft it.
我无法接受  那不是正大光明的击杀
I can't accept. It wasn't a noble kill.
敌人帮了我的忙
I was helped by an enemy.
为什么敌人会帮助你战斗
Why would an enemy help you in battle?
它不知道自己是我的敌人
It did not know it was my enemy.
既然你放弃印记
Since you forgo a signet,
我会用多余的资源铸造鸟哨
I shall use the excess to forge whistling birds.
鸟哨很不错
Whistling birds will do well.
为那些弃婴留一些
Reserve some for the foundlings.
本来就应该这样  弃婴才是未来
As it should always be. The foundlings are the future.
此乃正道
This is the Way.
鸟哨是一种能够抵挡多种敌人的强力防御装置
Whistling birds are a powerful defense against multiple enemies.
省着点用  因为它们很稀少
Use them sparingly, for they are rare.
我和你说过
Look, I told you.
我对你的借口没兴趣
I'm not interested in your excuses!
你已经试过了  吸尘怪  但你失败了
You had your shot, dust breather, but you failed.
你没有赏金碟了  赶紧出去
No pucks for you. Now get outta here.
曼达人
Mando!
他们都恨你  曼达人  因为你是传奇
They all hate you, Mando. Because you're a legend!
他们之中有多少人有追踪器
How many of them had tracking fobs?
他们都有  但他们没一个人完成了任务
All of them. All of them! But not one of them closed the deal.
只有你  曼达人  只有你
Only you, Mando. Only you.
有了它
And with it,
这个光年内最丰厚的奖赏
the richest reward this parsec has ever seen.
请坐  我的朋友
Please sit, my friend.
他们脑子里想的都是曼达洛铁  但我不是
They're all weighing the Beskar in their minds, but not me.
不  我庆祝你的成功
No. I, for one, I celebrate your success.
因为这也是我的成功
Because it is my success as well.
即使我很富有
Hell! Even I am rich.
如何才能向我最重要的合作伙伴表达感激呢
Now, how can I show my gratitude to my most valuable partner?
我要下一个任务
I want my next job.
下一个任务
Next job?
休息一会  好好享受一下
Take some time off. Enjoy yourself.
我带你去泡提列克疗伤浴
I'll take you to the Twi'lek healing baths.
我要下一个任务
I want my next job.
好吧
Sure. Fine.
你们这些赏金猎人就喜欢忙个不停  对吗
You hunters like to keep busy, right?
这些都在很远的地方
Well, these are all far away.
越远越好
The further, the better.
你选吧  这是你应得的
Well, take your pick. You've earned it.
这是最好的任务
Ah. That's the best one of the lot.
一个贵族的儿子在假释之后逃跑了
A nobleman's son skipped bail.
看来你得前往卡纳克的海丘
Looks like you're headed to the ocean dunes of Karnac.
你知道他们会怎么做吗
Any idea what they're gonna do with it?
什么怎么做
With what?
对那个孩子
The kid.
我没问  这违反公会规定
I didn't ask. It's against the Guild Code.
他们为帝国工作
They work for the Empire.
他们在那里干什么
What are they doing here?
已经没有帝国了  曼达人
The Empire is gone, Mando.
只留下了佣兵和军阀
All that are left are mercenaries and warlords.
如果你介意
But if it bothers you,
返回核心区域  把他们汇报给新共和国
just go back to the Core and report them to the New Republic.
真是笑话
That's a joke.
曼达人  去享受你的奖赏吧
Mando, enjoy your rewards.
去买一瓶香料吧
Buy a camtono of spice.
你从脱离曲速之后
By the time you come out of hyperdrive,
你肯定就已经全忘了
you will have forgotten all about it.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我命令你取出必要的材料
I order you to extract the necessary material
然后就行了
and be done with it.
他很明确地命令我们
He has explicitly ordered us
要抓活的回来
to bring it back alive.
快点搞定你的任务
Finish your business quickly,
因为我不能再保证你的安全了
as I no longer can guarantee your safety.
检查周围
Check the perimeter.
不不不  求你了  不不不
No, no, no, no, please. Please. No. No, no.
不  求你
No, please.
别伤害它  它只是个孩子
Please don't hurt him. It's just a child.
求你了  不要
Please. No. No! Please. No. No, no.
你把它怎么了  你把它怎么了
What did you do to it? What did you do it?
我保护了它  我保护了它
I protected him. I protected him.
没有我在的话  它现在已经死了
If it wasn't for me, he would already be dead!
求你  求你
Please! Please. Please.
看  那里
Look, there!
分头行动  我们逼他出来
Split up. We'll flush him out.
放弃吧  没有地方可...
Give it up. There's nowhere to...
站住
Hey!
不许动
Freeze!
Don't move.
举起手来
Hands up.
把枪放下
Drop the blaster.
等等  我手里的东西很有价值
Wait. What I'm holding is very valuable.
在这里
Here.
转过来对着我
Now turn and face me.
站起来
Stand up!
欢迎回来  曼达人
Welcome back, Mando!
把猎物放下吧
Now put the package down.
让开  我要去我的飞船
Step aside. I'm going to my ship.
你把猎物放下  我可能会让你过去
You put the bounty down and perhaps I'll let you pass.
这孩子跟我走
The kid's coming with me.
如果你真的在意这孩子
If you truly care about the kid,
就把它放在陆行艇上
then you'll put it on the speeder
我们再谈条件
and we'll discuss terms.
我怎么知道能不能相信你
How do I know I can trust you?
因为我是你唯一的希望了
Because I'm your only hope.
开车
Drive.
快开车
Drive!
武器真棒啊
That's one impressive weapon!
接下来我会这么做
Here's what I'll do.
我要带这孩子去飞船上
I'm gonna walk to my ship with the kid
你必须让我过去
and you're gonna let it happen.
不行  这样怎么样
No. How about this?
我们把孩子带走
We take the kid,
如果你想阻止我们  我们就杀了你
and if you try to stop us, we kill you
然后把你身上能用的部件都搜刮走
and we strip your body for parts.
别打中目标
Don't hit the target!
快跑  我们掩护
Get out of here! We'll hold them off!
你得把神秘人物转移了
You're going to have to relocate the covert.
此乃正道
This is the way.
站住  曼达人
Hold it, Mando.
我不想让事情发展成这样
I didn't want it to come to this.
可你违背了条约
But then you broke the Code.
我也得来个那种装备
I gotta get one of those.